INDOXXI
Support dengan like & share :)
A powerful
new strain of influenza
has killed more
than 5,000 people in Egypt,
according to reports out
of Cairo.
New cases of Saharan flu
were reported in France,
Spain, Germany, and Italy.
The flu is spreading
beyond doctors' abilities
to contain it.
The flu
has reached U.S. shores,
with cases reported in...
We have reports
that a million
have died in the Middle East.
...and San Francisco.
We have reports
that a million have died...
The World Health Organization
warns that this could be
a civilization-ending event.
...this could be
Riots are breaking out
across the country,
as people desperately try
to secure
life-support bunkers
for their families.
To ensure survival
of the human race.
The World Health Organization
has started construction
on half a million
underground bunkers.
Scientists are searching
desperately for a cure,
but they warn
that Saharan flu mortality
could be 100 percent.
Authorities promise
lottery winners
will have access to bunkers
within 24 hours.
...survive.
With an estimated
three billion dead worldwide,
it is unclear if the bunkers
will be finished in time.
Authorities promise
lottery winners
will have access to bunkers
within 24 hours.
This is our final broadcast.
Good luck, and Godspeed.
I'm thoroughly disgusted.
I-- I don't even know
if I can look at you the sa--
Cool it! You're gonna
give yourself a stroke.
And at your age, Atlanta,
you need
- to take care of yourself.
- You seem very calm
for someone who just confessed
to murder.
I mean, I get bored.
I do-- I do some bad shit.
Ain't never hurt none of y'all.
You've hurt us now.
Now we can't pretend
- you're not such a bad guy.
- Come on.
- You knew I was a bad guy.
- Right.
But now we can't pretend--
You know,
I'm-- I'm almost flattered
by that, Denver, but, honestly,
I could care less
what you think.
You couldn't care less.
- What?
- The phrase,
it's you couldn't care less.
Saying you could care less means
that you actually care.
Well, how
about I don't give a rat's ass?
- You like that, Denver?
- That's actually better.
- Congratulations.
- You starting shit
just for kicks, Orlando?
That's classy, man.
Keeping it mature.
What, you think I'm here
to entertain y'all?
Nah. Just think
you're one fucked-up dude.
You sure you're not talking
about yourself there, hombre?
Hey, only God can judge us, man.
You know, I've been staring
at your boring, mopey faces
on this little digital box
for half a decade.
I mean, it's time for a change,
right?
Some truth, some honesty.
You don't give a shit
about honesty.
You just like the sound
of your own voice.
That hurts me, Chicago.
I value honesty.
It's what separates the men
from children.
Hmm, real men don't lie.
Is that it?
Yeah,
that's what little, uh,
pissy babies like you say,
right?
That's why you're a child...
and I'm a man.
You never did fit in with us.
- This explains so much.
- Ah, that really means a lot
coming from you there, Atlanta.
I mean, there's no way
in hell you could survive
- out there in the real world.
- We are all survivors.
I'm talking about living
in the shit.
Atlanta here,
she ain't never lived
- in no shit!
- It's no excuse
- for what you've done.
- But least I own it!
How many people
have you killed, anyway?
Ah, to be honest, 15.
I don't know. Maybe 20,
if you want to be real.
- Oh, my God.
- "Oh, my God." Are you serious?
Come on. Most of them
were bank robberies gone bad.
Okay, I'm sorry. Hold on.
There was a time that I did it
for sport,
and to tell you the truth,
it was actually fun.
I am trying to find a way
to pray for your soul...
but I'm not even sure
if you have one.
Oh, and this is coming
from the mother of the year.
What's it like to, uh,
think about those three
precious angels
up there,
dead with everyone else?
- How dare you?
- No, I mean, I'm just asking.
I mean, they were--
They were kids, right?
I mean, that is a hell of a way
to go, especially being so young.
Dude!
Too far, man. That's fucked up.
But that's what I'm talking
about. It's the truth!
Hey, the truth!
And none of you want to hear it!
You know what? You're right.
I don't want to hear it.
I have a proposal
for the Domain.
Oh, here it comes,
the bullshit democracy.
Since day one,
Orlando's been nothing
but a thorn in our sides
and now he's confessing
to brutally murdering
innocent people.
No, no, no.
They weren't all innocent.
We don't have
to listen to it anymore.
We can just ban him
and shut off his feed for good.
Ah! I love it! You can't ban me.
- I can.
- For real?
You can just shut us off
at any time?
It's not that simple, okay?
It's-- It's a hack I came across
after studying the code
for years,
but that doesn't mean
I agree with Boston.
Banning someone is permanent.
We can't come back from it,
so we have to make sure
that this is something
we all wanna do.
So that's why we vote.
It's what we do.
Oh, this-- This here,
is a frigging joke.
I have to listen
to this blah-blah-blah bullshit,
day in and day out.
Banning me is not a punishment.
Orlando, banning you
is permanent.
No contact with anybody
for the rest
of your time down here.
That could mean
more than 20 years.
Well, that to me, sounds
like a 20-year vacation.
Who votes to ban Orlando
from the Domain?
I do.
- Me.
- We need one more. Phoenix?
- This feels wrong.
- Be reasonable.
- It's extreme.
- He's extreme.
- No, I can't do it.
- Come on.
He could be alone for decades.
It's not fair.
Maybe he deserves it.
I'm sorry. I can't sign off
on this. No. I vote no.
Denver, I'm assuming
you're voting with Phoenix.
Yes, I am.
That's two against three.
Houston... you're it.
What's it gonna be?
Ah, fuck, man, I don't--
I don't wanna be the last vote.
- You gotta do it.
- Shit.
I can't, man. I ca--
I can't vote.
You know, let me make this easy
for all of you.
Do it.
- Ban me.
- Wow. I wasn't expecting that.
Shut him down.
No, I won't do it
until Phoenix says it's okay.
It's not up to her. We voted.
It's over.
He's right, Denver.
It's not up to me.
Unplug it, Denver.
Did I ever tell you guys
I'm a psychic?
I could read minds
and the future.
You want me to tell you
what the future holds
- for all of you?
- Denver, unplug him now.
Pain and suffering,
a life of shit
like you could never imagine,
nothing but pure misery.
And you know what really--
It pisses me off,
because I'm not gonna be here
to witness it.
Done.
Amen.
You awake?
Yeah.
How you feeling?
Pretty restless.
Yeah. Today was, uh,
was rough.
Mm-hmm.
Did you agree with me?
Yeah, of course.
I wouldn't have done it
unless you said it was okay.
I know.
But did you actually agree
with my point?
Yeah. I mean, I was...
I was torn. You know, I can see
where the others
are coming from.
People make mistakes.
We've all made mistakes.
So no one
should ever be punished?
I'm not saying that, no.
I guess
I just don't feel comfortable...
judging.
You gotta remember, Phoenix,
he's not dead.
Okay? He's still in a bunker
in Florida in some marsh,
spouting his redneck bullshit
philosophies to himself,
so don't lose
too much sleep over it.
And who knows? This could
be over in a year, right?
Wouldn't even matter.
That would be so nice.
Do you ever think about just
what it would be like to...
be in the same room together...
all the time?
No more... screens...
be able to touch you?
- Never.
- Mm.
Of course I do.
It's what keeps me
looking forward to the future.
I love you, Phoenix.
I love you, too.
Please dispense Supplival.
Supplival dispensed.
- Morning.
- Hey.
- Did you sleep okay?
- Not really.
Was it another dream
about your mom?
What about your mom?
Well, thank you
for interrupting, Boston.
Morning to you, too, Denver.
You know, do you ever consider--
I don't know,
maybe not barging in
on a private conversation?
Hey, if you two have
a secret to share,
you can always start
your own chat room.
Common feed is fair game.
Oh, wow.
This migraine.
Eighty percent
of migraines result
- from dehydration.
- That statistic reeks of B.S.
- Can you prove me wrong?
- Yeah,
but I don't have time.
Good morning, angels.
Mommy has a headache.
Fuck, man!
Fuck! This sleep cycle's
fucking bullshit!
Look what the cat dragged in.
Get off my back, Boston.
Slept like shit.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you looked hung over.
Man, I wish.
Uh, wow,
like a couple of bottles
and some bitches, shit.
We could have ourselves
a party, right, Atlanta?
You know what, Houston?
I'm not even gonna dignify that
- with a response.
- Aw, you love me.
Oh, fuck!
God, I hope this fucking shit
doesn't keep up.
You can't sleep,
put a blanket over your head.
Fuck, I'll put a blanket
over your mom's head.
The sleep cycle
doesn't just affect
the lighting, okay?
It--
It affects your inner clock.
- Yeah, what Denver said.
- Oh, yeah, I forgot.
Denver is the resident expert
on everything.
- Well, you said it, not me.
- Chicago.
- Nice of you to join us.
- Give me a break.
Think I have a cold.
You're in a hermetically
sealed environment, so...
that's actually,
physically impossible.
Well,
something's making me sick.
Maybe you should drink
a fucking Supplival,
get some meat
on your weak-ass bones.
- Back off.
- All this doom and gloom.
Everybody cheer up.
We're alive another day.
- Happy now?
- Oui, monsieur.
Phoenix, you still working
on your French?
Oui. C'est bien. Et tu?
Uh, les chatons son...
mignons?
Did you just say that kittens
are cute?
That's, um,
not what I meant to say.
- Well, what did you mean to say?
- Doesn't really matter.
- I'm still learning.
- You know, you've been learning
for two years now
- with no visible progress.
- Denver.
I don't study every day.
- This is just for fun.
- I'm sure that's why you do it.
What's that supposed to mean?
While you two are busy bickering
like an old married couple,
I'm gonna go ahead
and do my morning prayers.
Anybody care to join?
Every morning
you ask us if we wanna pray
and the answer is always
the same.
Isn't that the definition
of psychosis?
I'll pray with you.
- Really?
- Sure.
I don't know any prayers,
though.
That's okay.
Uh, I can send you one.
It's one that, uh,
I used to do with my girls
just before I put them to bed.
Got it?
- Yep.
- Okay.
- O Lord, make me brave.
- Make me brave.
Brave enough to face the dark,
the dark that works
to pull me in.
As the storm rages through...
let me rise above the gale
with bright eyes,
confident Thy way is wise.
Lord, make me brave...
brave to face the murk of life.
Help me with my human plight.
Help me to retain my sight...
to know that from the dark
comes light.
To know that
from the dark comes light.
- Amen.
Thanks, Phoenix. That was nice.
Very nice. Touching, even.
All right, everybody,
let's get ready for the day.
Morning reports, let's hear 'em.
Okay, the Network neutralized
almost three billion
Saharan flu particles overnight.
That's a .009 increase
from yesterday.
A slight uptick.
That's the good news.
Bad news is that works out
to about 19 years
- before total containment.
- Oh, God damn!
I hope that shit picks up
the pace, man.
Well, there was that one night
where it jumped up
a whole percentage point.
Atlanta's on the right track.
We have to stay optimistic
because we do not know
what's gonna happen tomorrow.
Probably nothing,
just like yesterday
and the day before that,
day before that,
Atlanta, you're up.
Okay,
so blood scans look normal.
Except, Phoenix,
your pressure's up.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Maybe I'm not reading it right,
but your brain scan
looks kinda weird.
Maybe someone else should, uh,
- read the brain scan.
- Hey, man, fuck you.
- I can read this.
- Just had a bad dream,
and I'm feeling kind of out
of it. It's probably just that.
Was the bad dream
about your mom?
I'd rather not talk
about it right now.
- Jesus, Boston.
- I'm sorry.
- Wow, that was-- That was rude.
- Anyway, moving on.
Bunker population is 489,573,
which is down eight
from yesterday.
That's not good.
- It's probably just a bad night.
- This is so stupid.
We're all looking
at the same numbers
on this tiny, little screen.
Why are we pretending
like we have separate jobs?
Because we have to keep focused.
Each one of us has one statistic
to keep an eye on.
- I don't.
- Yeah, because you didn't wanna
- participate, remember?
- Because it's a waste of time.
No, it is not!
- Ah, shit, no, man.
- You did that on purpose.
Do you
like wasting your life? Here.
Watch an instructional video
you've seen a thousand times.
You need
a serious attitude adjustment.
I'm out. I'll see you in, like,
five minutes.
Why can't you get
this stupid thing to stop?
I thought you'd really,
really like it.
Hello. My name is Nadine,
and I am the designer
of the LSB-300
life-support bunker.
If you're watching this,
the lottery is over
and you are one of the lucky few
who will live through
the Saharan flu epidemic.
You are a survivor.
If need be,
your bunker can keep you alive
for up to 70 years.
Yeah, I tell you,
I ain't gonna last 70 hours
if this shit don't stop.
It'll work itself out.
Just calm down.
Oh, you want to trade bunkers?
To protect you
from surface conditions,
your bunker
is 30 feet underground.
The artificial day cycle
will keep
your sleep patterns normal.
Your bunker is stocked
with enough Supplival powder
to last a lifetime.
When mixed with water,
Supplival creates
a delicious shake
that's packed with nutrients
in vanilla, strawberry
or chocolate.
This is so not
a chocolate shake.
The generator powers
the bunker's closed-loop air
and water filtration.
One hundred percent
of what you consume is recycled.
Wait a minute. Does that mean
we drink our own piss?
You just now realized that?
Science is amazing.
The Generator
also powers
the atmosphere purifier.
The purifier filters
contaminated air molecules
and strips them off the virus.
The 500,000 bunkers
that make up the network,
operate in tandem
to eliminate the viral threat.
The network generates
an estimate
for how long this process
will take based on daily data,
which you can view
on your statistics terminal.
Solitary habitation is necessary
to ensure that the virus
spreads no further.
To combat the inevitable sense
of isolation,
we created Domain.
Domain is an information
and social networking platform.
Domain also allows full access
to our encyclopedia archives.
Studies found that groups
of seven
create an ideal long-term
social-networking community.
Each group of seven was selected
using algorithms derived
from your personal histories.
Right now, I, too,
am probably living out my days
in an LSB-300 just like yours,
wondering how much longer
I'll be down here.
One thing is certain:
we will eradicate
the Saharan flu.
Your efforts matter. You matter.
We are the survivors.
An Earth free
of this virus awaits.
Humanity is counting on us.
What is it?
I was just thinking,
when we finally get out
of here...
are we gonna call each other
by our real names?
Dean Atkins.
It sounds so strange
coming out of your mouth.
Say mine.
Kimberly Miller.
That sounds so weird.
Let's just stick
with our handles.
Warning. Warning.
Warning. Power backup
below 50 percent.
Charge generator immediately.
Atlanta,
you gotta make this a routine.
- You can't skip any more days.
- I know. I know.
Its's not like I have to watch
my figure for anybody down here.
Warning.
Power backup below 50 percent.
Charge generator immediately.
- Do you guys see this?
- What is it?
My terminal's freaking out.
Oh, that is weird. Mine, too.
Well, now it's--
Now it's totally dead.
- What the fuck?
- This a glitch?
Maybe it's just rebooting.
No, mine's--
Mine's completely off.
This is not good.
These are supposed to be
on all the time.
That's-- That's the whole point,
live data.
Fuck is going on?
I mean, first my sleep cycle?
Now this bullshit?
This is affecting all of us.
You know, your sleep cycle,
that's probably just
a malfunction.
How the hell do you know that?
How do you know
someone's not just fucking
with me on purpose?
- Who would do that?
- How about Orlando?
He fucking hates us for sure.
That's it, guys. The end of days
are upon us.
Could really do
without your sarcasm right now.
- I'm not being sarcastic.
- You know, I don't know, guys.
This is making me kind of worry.
Relax. It'll probably
come back on in a minute.
Probably? What do you mean,
"Probably"?
We have no idea
if it'll come back on.
- I'm an optimistic guy.
- We are spread out
over the entire country.
You understand there's no--
There's no actual physical wires
connecting our bunkers.
This has to be
a systemic shutdown.
It's pure speculation.
You know,
for a self-appointed leader,
you are depressingly short
on actual ideas.
Okay, well,
what brilliant suggestions
- do you have then, Denver?
- I'm not saying
I have one. I just don't think
sticking your head in the sand
should be an option.
I think we should turn
Orlando's feedback on.
- What? No-- No!
- Why?
Maybe we broke the system
when we banned him.
Think about it.
There are supposed
to be seven of us and right now,
there are only six.
- Maybe we caused the glitch.
- That is pretty thin.
We banned him.
We don't want him here!
Listen, Atlanta, I know.
I don't like him either...
but without the terminal,
we're blind to everything
that's going on outside.
Bringing Orlando back
might fix the problem.
- No, we voted on this.
- Yeah, like, eight months ago.
The ban, it was--
It was permanent.
Denver...
you out of all people
have gotta be able to figure
that out.
No, I-- I really don't think
that's possible.
Really?
Seriously,
you're not even gonna try.
Yeah, okay...
I'll try but I'm telling you,
everything I know
says that this isn't gonna work.
Well, there you go.
It's a nonissue.
Fine.
Phoenix, what are you doing?
Stop. You--
You already did that today.
Phoenix.
Listen, it doesn't store
extra energy or...
Phoenix.
- Phoenix, why are you mad?
- Because you won't even try.
- I sa-- I will try.
- But it won't work.
And so if you don't think
it's gonna work,
then you're not gonna
make it work.
Will you s...
Phoenix, will you stop, please?
Please, just sit down
and talk to me.
I want to help, okay?
Do you?
Yes. Why would you say that?
Of course I do.
Then let me do this
at my own pace.
Okay. I'm not...
trying to force anything.
I-- I just wanna help.
I don't know
where to start.
This is about your mom, right?
My mom isn't alive.
Yeah, I know.
I mean, she wasn't alive
before all this.
I...
I was in prison
when I won the lottery.
Really?
What happened?
I never knew my dad,
'cause he died when I was young.
My mom raised me alone.
She worked constantly,
'cause she had to.
I spent a lot
of my teenage years alone...
got in with a bad crowd...
got into drugs, mostly meth.
I lied, stole...
ran away from home
when I was 17...
came back when I OD'ed.
Didn't stop.
Uh, one night...
I got high...
paranoid...
accused my mom
of stealing my stash.
Um...
I went down to the kitchen...
grabbed a paring knife...
went back up the stairs
and I-- I stabbed her.
Uh, the drugs were
in my room where I left 'em.
I'm so sorry, Phoenix.
I wish I could hold you
right now.
When did this happen?
I was in prison a year
when the flu hit,
so almost seven years ago now.
The whole Orlando thing
makes a lot of sense now.
Banning him was wrong.
Who am I to judge?
Phoenix, it's not the same.
Yeah, you're right.
What I did was worse.
- Phoenix--
- I'm not looking
for your sympathy.
Lifting the ban on Orlando
is the right thing to do.
Okay.
Okay, you're right.
I will do everything I can
to lift the ban.
I'm lucky to have you here
with me.
I'm the lucky one.
- Phoenix!
- Mm.
- Mm, what's going on?
- Phoenix, hey.
I-- I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
- Um...
- What time is it?
It's-- It's early-- Late.
It's late, maybe. I don't know.
I don't know. I've been working
on lifting this ban thing,
but I think I--
I figured it out.
- Did you have any luck?
- I'm not 100 percent sure
that this is gonna work, but...
there is a possibility
that I-- I could ban myself
- or one of you guys.
- Okay, well, don't do that.
I know. I--
I don't want to do that,
but are you sure
that we shouldn't tell
the others about this?
Why? So Boston
can tell us not to do it?
- I mean, what's the point?
- Yeah.
Okay. You're right.
You're right. Um...
Here we go.
Orlando.
Orlando, are you there?
Orlando, it's--
It's Phoenix and Denver.
We turned your feed back on.
Can you hear us?
- What are you doing?
- I'm checking the logs
for information.
Come on. Say something.
There's-- There's nothing here.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
I'm just looking to see
if I can find something.
There's gotta be something.
- Where is he?
- Maybe he...
- escaped?
- Maybe he's dead.
We have to tell the others.
I'm really disappointed
in both of you.
I thought
that you'd show more respect
for our system,
which we all agreed on,
- by the way.
- We just felt this
was important enough
to make our own decision.
That's not how we do things!
We put you in charge
six years ago.
Maybe it's time we change
some of these old rules.
Oh, I see how you wanna play it.
You wanna be in charge?
Why does anybody have
to be in charge?
I think it's important
that we have a leader.
I mean, personally,
I find it comforting.
You can't figure out what's up
on your own?
Why are you antagonizing me?
- I'm just asking a question.
- No.
- Now you're being disingenuous.
- From where I'm sitting, Boston,
he-- He's not in charge
of fucking jack shit, man.
Look, I am really sorry
about your sleep cycle.
I wish there was something
I could do about it.
Stop fucking changing!
You're fucking-- I can't!
Stop fucking changing,
you broken piece
of fucking shit!
Houston, calm down.
You're not helping.
I don't give a shit.
I've been awake
for three fucking days.
I'm losing my fucking mind.
This is fucking Orlando.
That's what it is.
What?
What are you talking about?
He's fucking mad at me,
'cause I fucking voted him out
and now he's fucking with me.
Houston, Houston,
you didn't vote against him.
You didn't vote at all.
Remember?
He voted himself out.
Whoever built this shit,
he's fucking tough, bro.
And he's fucking--
He's doing this shit to me
on purpose...
'cause he fucking hates me.
I mean,
why else is my sleep cycle
fucking doing this shit?
There's a hundred reasons
it could be broken, Houston.
Please, sit down.
I don't like seeing you
like this.
Is there any chance
that Orlando can actually be
in there somewhere?
I mean, there's a possibility
he could be dead or...
I don't know,
hiding from the camera,
but that doesn't seem
like his personality.
Well, what if he tried
to escape?
How could he escape?
The doors are locked.
Has anyone tried their door
since the terminal shut down?
What if it actually opens?
You could be exposed.
Phoenix! Don't.
Phoenix, wait-- Wait-- Wait!
No, no, no! What are--
Think about it!
Think about what you're doing.
Stop!
Hey.
Hi.
I'm trying to be zen
about what you and Denver did.
We agreed on a hierarchy
way back when all this started,
but all of a sudden,
you and Denver,
you guys decided
to do your own thing.
Well, we've been in here
for years.
Things can't stay
the same forever.
But that doesn't mean
you should do whatever you want,
- whenever you want.
- You know that lifting
the ban on Orlando
was the smart thing to do.
You sound more and more like him
as the years roll on.
- Like who?
- Denver.
I mean, you're two peas
in a pod.
Well, it's no secret
we're together.
"Together."
I mean, what does
that even mean down here?
It means we see a future
with one another.
I will never understand,
why him?
- As opposed to you?
- No, I me-- I mean, that's--
- that's not what I mean.
- I'm sorry to be blunt,
but it's absolutely none
of your business.
Look, I'm just worried
about you, okay?
I mean, there's something
about him
that gives me the creeps.
Don't you see that?
No, I don't.
He's never been anything
but supportive and loving.
You never even met him
in person.
I never met you in person
and you expect me to trust you.
What is this about, Boston?
Denver reminds me
of my dad,
his looks, his voice,
his mannerisms, everything.
You know, on the surface,
he's really friendly,
super smart, and charming,
but there was something
really fake about it all.
I mean, he was mean as shit
behind closed doors.
You hit this switch
and, snap, he was a monster.
Listen, I always appreciate
your honesty,
and thank you for your concern,
but I know Denver,
and he is nothing like...
your father.
Okay.
What are you thinking
about right now?
You.
I know, but what,
specifically?
What it would feel like...
to have my hands all
over your body.
What else?
What your lips would taste like.
And?
What your...
What you would feel like
underneath me.
Taste of your sweat. Mm.
How hard are you fucking me?
Oh, I'm fucking you so hard.
I'm thinking
about you looking back at me.
You gonna come?
I want you to come.
How was that?
Oh, man.
Oh, I hope nobody plays
that back.
Who cares if they do?
I love you so much.
Denver.
Hi.
Mm.
Are you reading?
No. No, I was just--
I was at the pool,
- thought I'd do a couple laps.
- Nice.
Oh, let me guess.
You're reading, uh, No Exit.
How many times
have you read that?
I don't know. I lost count.
- Wow. It's that good, huh?
- Yeah. I like it.
You know, it's a--
It's a classic.
What's up?
Do you remember
when we used to record
those private videos?
I do, yeah.
What if Orlando made some
of his own while he was banned?
Do you think
you could access them?
Yeah. I mean,
if they're not hidden very well.
Um...
While I'm doing this,
what made you...
wanna watch those videos?
Just wanted to think
about something nice.
So a video of me getting off,
that-- That did the trick?
Oh, totally.
Okay. I got some, uh,
right here.
Oh, I got a bunch. Okay, I--
I'll screen-share it with you.
This one's
from a couple months ago.
Play it.
Day 121. I feel amazing.
I don't think I've ever been
in better shape.
He seems fine.
Guess he wasn't lying
when he said
he wouldn't miss us.
- Well, that was uneventful.
- Play a different one.
Okay.
I did not realize he was such
a workout enthusiast.
Day 186.
Guess what.
I'm gonna be a frigging Hulk
when I get out of here, huh?
Huh?
Oh, I guess...
There's--
There's hundreds of these.
Yeah, it's like Orlando's video
workout series.
Okay, here's the last one.
It's from a few days ago.
It's a much bigger file.
What is this?
I don't know.
Leave me alone!
Wait. What just happened?
I don't understand.
He-- He's gone.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
Look at his door.
His door is open.
What do you mean it's--
That's not--
That's not possible.
Wait. Go back to the static.
There. Did you hear that?
- What?
- Yeah. What is that?
- Sounds like screaming.
- Is that Orlando?
- How long is this video?
- It's long.
There's five hours of this.
- Go to the very end.
- Hang on.
See, what I think
is that Orlando set
this whole thing up, all right?
He's the one--
He's the one who put us in here.
He tricked us into thinking
that the Saharan flu is real
and then he made us
wait down here for five years.
- That's a little implausible.
- Houston,
can you try to calm down?
No, you guys don't see it,
but I do, okay?
It makes total fucking sense
to me now,
all right?
This is what he wanted.
He wanted for all of us
to go fucking crazy, okay?
But I fucking-- I got it,
all right? I figured it out,
'cause I-- I see what he's doing
to us.
Houston, how long
has it been since you slept?
Who the fuck knows, man?
Fuck sleep.
I don't need sleep. Sleep is
for weak-ass motherfuckers
like you guys, okay?
But Orlando's plan,
it blew up in his fucking face,
man,
because I can see
what he fucking did to us, man.
Okay, so this is
a big conspiracy theory.
No, it's not a theory, man.
- I know I'm right.
- You know you're right,
from what, from a--
A door shutting in a video?
You're just too fucking afraid
to fucking admit it, man.
Will you please stop cursing?
My goodness,
you're making my head spin.
Maybe you need an exorcism.
Sweetie, how about contributing
something useful
to a stressful situation?
- This video could be fake.
- How?
- And why?
- That's my point.
- We don't know anything.
- So, what, let me guess.
Your idea is to-- To just
sit here and do nothing?
- What other choice do we have?
- Well, you could be
forcibly removed
like Orlando was.
That is pure speculation.
How many times
can you say the same thing?
As many times as I have to
to get you to listen to reason.
Maybe the terminal shut down,
because we don't
need it anymore.
- Maybe the flu is gone.
- Yeah, Atlanta,
maybe we'll all be saved.
Maybe in a few days,
we'll just walk out of here
and everything'll be perfect.
You know,
maybe your little angels
- are alive and all grown up.
- Are you done yet?
Are you done
with your little tantrum?
We need to take action
while we still have control.
Hey, Phoenix, man,
I hate to break it to you,
but we ain't in control of shit,
all right?
Orlando, Orlando's running
this whole fucking game, man.
- He got us beat.
- I hope you're right, Houston.
I really do.
Because that's better
than the alternative.
Well, do you have a plan,
Phoenix?
Yeah. I think we should find
a way out.
You all sound crazy to me.
Maybe the lock that seals
the door can be broken.
Sudden depressurization
could be fatal.
Well, that's a risk
that I'm willing to take.
- In here, we're safe.
- We're not safe
- and that video is proof.
- It doesn't prove
anything. I'm still
not convinced it's real.
What else do you need?
We don't know what's going on.
- We have to do something.
- Okay. Let's vote.
I don't need your permission
to make my own plan.
- Can I have two votes?
- Houston, concentrate.
Stop, officer. Don't shoot me.
I used to say
that shit all the time
when I was a kid.
Hey, you guys ever have
- the cops put a gun on you?
- Houston!
Fuck, man! Fuck, yeah! We escape
and go find that
lying motherfucker, Orlando!
We skin him alive! Sounds like
a fuckin' plan to me!
- He's lost his mind.
- I lost my mind,
then I found it.
It's right here in my head.
Listen, we can't make
any decisions
with Houston like this.
Good evening.
Hi.
What are you doing up?
You know, just checking in.
- Can you even see anything?
- Sort of.
Figured I'd do Boston the favor
of not searching...
- directly in front of his face.
- That's very sweet.
Did you find anything yet?
Nope, not really.
Uh, you know,
it is the middle of the night,
so maybe you should try
and get some sleep.
Yeah.
I can't really sleep.
What's up?
I was trying to remember...
what everyone's real name is.
There's, uh, Barry.
- Raymond.
- Olivia.
- Cedric.
- And then...
Houston.
- What's his real name?
- Huh.
I don't think he ever told us.
Do you hear that?
Yeah, what is that?
Houston.
Oh, no.
What is going on?
Oh, shit.
Houston, stop.
Houston.
What the...
You still think we're safe
in here, Boston?
I'm scared.
Me, too.
Who are they?
I don't know. I don't...
People immune
to the Saharan flu? I...
How are they
finding the bunkers?
Maybe they heard
Houston screaming.
I don't know. Let's just...
Let's try and get some rest,
okay?
- Okay.
- Good night.
Good night.
No.
Phoenix.
Don't move.
- What's wrong?
- Slowly look down...
but be very careful.
You guys scared
the hell out of me.
It's just a little rat. Hi.
Don't touch it.
It could be sick.
No.
Only humans can get Saharan flu.
- I'm talking about rabies.
- Hey there, little guy.
Come here.
How did it get there?
Aren't these things supposed
to be sealed?
Oh, my God, Atlanta.
It's a miracle.
No, no, Phoenix, Phoenix,
she's right.
You need to be careful.
Your bunker is not airtight.
I think this is my fault.
I found this panel yesterday
and tried to pry it open.
The rat must have knocked it out
when it came in.
- What were you looking for?
- A way out.
"Emergency vent."
Can you see anything?
No. There's nothing.
Do you guys have the same panel?
I don't-- I don't understand.
- This doesn't make any sense.
- You know,
maybe it's some kind
of ventilation system
- that connects all the bunkers.
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah, there's ventilation ducts
across
the entire continental U.S.
You know what?
Stop being an asshole.
I'm just brainstorming.
Yeah, but aren't we
30 feet underground?
Yeah, that's--
That's my point, okay?
Th-- There should be dirt
on the other side of this wall,
not an open space
and definitely not a vent.
Does this make you guys happy...
asking all these questions?
Like, do you feel like
you're making progress?
Do you feel like you're solving
some mystery?
So tell me, what is your idea,
hmm, Chicago?
Nothing. Do nothing.
Same shit's gonna happen,
regardless.
For once, I agree with Chicago.
- I think we should wait it out.
- Of course,
you think we should wait.
That's your answer
to everything!
Sit back and wait.
Well, you know what?
We've been listening to you
this entire time and every day
has gotten progressively worse.
So, what, you think we could have
done something about Orlando?
You think we could have done
something about Houston?
About the rat? About fucking...
- Stop arguing!
- ...any of this?
What we need right now
is more information.
Great idea. Just simply acquire
more information.
Look, we know
that we're connected
to the Domain network.
There has gotta be a way
to access data
- from the other bunkers.
- Even if it works,
- what will it accomplish?
- I don't know, but maybe
we can contact someone else.
That could work. I'll--
I'll get on it.
Now, I think everyone else
should start going
- around the bunker--
- Who put you in charge?
I'm taking charge,
because no one else is doing it.
- Maybe we should vote.
- Boston, stop wasting time.
- Look, I'm the one that got--
- Stop!
- The system is collapsing.
- The system is collapsed.
Which is why we need
to find a way out of here.
- How?
- I'm not sure.
An emergency release?
Something.
I don't know.
There's gotta be a way.
Okay. Okay, okay, just,
you know, tell me
where to start. I'll help.
Be creative. Try-- Try anything.
Boston, you, too.
- Chicago, you gonna help us out?
- Sorry.
- I don't do jailbreaks.
- Come on.
- You're a smart guy.
- Leave me alone.
What exactly are we looking
for again?
Can you guys--
Can you just keep it down?
I'm trying to focus.
Oh, I'm sorry, princess.
Atlanta, what are you doing?
The Supplival has to be coming
from someplace.
I think it's connected
to that pipe back there.
I'm gonna break through.
I think there's something
- on the other side.
- Atlanta, if you break that,
you could cut access
to your food.
Yeah, I agree
with Boston.
I know I told you
to try anything but--
No.
No, guys. Listen, if I'm gonna
end up starving to death,
then I guess that was God's plan
for me all along.
- What do you see?
- Nothing.
It's just empty space.
- You can't see anything?
- No. It's pitch-black.
But there's too much space
on the other side of this wall.
It doesn't make sense.
Atlanta, your door.
Atlanta!
O Lord, make me brave,
brave enough to face the dark,
the dark that works
to pull me in.
Help me to retain my sight,
to see that from the dark
comes light.
Oh, no. No. Oh, God.
To know that from the dark
comes light.
Chicago...
what are you doing?
- Denver!
- What?
- Atlanta's gone.
- What? When?
Look at Chicago's feed.
Is that Supplival?
He was starving himself.
Chicago, please, don't do this.
We can get through this,
Chicago.
Nobody's getting through.
We need you.
That's not true.
Chicago, you don't wanna
do this. You don't.
I never wanted
to do anything more.
Goodbye, guys.
Please, Chicago, don't do this.
No. No! No.
No.
God.
I can't look at that.
Then don't.
Why are you so fucking cold?
I'm dealing with this
in my own way, all right?
Why don't you show some emotion,
you fucking robot?
He was our friend.
Hi.
Well, I hate to bring
this down even further,
but I have some new information.
New information
would be good right now.
Well, that depends
on your point of view.
So, the bunkers,
they're all connected, right?
Every bunker in the Network
has its own feed.
That's 500,000 feeds.
So the Domain,
what it does is it limits access
to the seven people
in your group.
The feeds, they're still there
but you just can't see 'em.
Well,
can you access them now?
Yeah. I already did.
I can only pull 'em up one
at a time. This is, uh,
this is a random one.
I'm-- I'm assuming
they already took this person.
Who is that?
- No idea.
- Why can't we hear him?
I couldn't locate
the audio streams, video only,
so we can't communicate
with them and...
they can't see us.
- So this is live.
- Yeah.
Wow.
It is so weird to see a new face
after all these years.
God.
I've seen a lot of suicides.
This-- This-- This is just...
- I don't know.
- There's more.
What?
There's only
a thousand feeds
coming from the main server.
- So what?
- There should be 500,000,
one from each bunker.
Is it possible that you
just can't access them all?
No. No. I mean,
I-- I didn't think
that it was possible,
so I-- I triple-checked it
but I'm telling you...
there's only a thousand bunkers.
- What does that mean?
- It means they lied to us.
We have to get out of here.
How?
When we were searching
the bunkers,
I found this cluster
of wires connecting...
the door to the computer.
So we-- If we cut it,
the computer loses control
of the door?
Yeah. It just might unlock it.
Or we cut power to a crucial
life-support function,
and we starve or suffocate
in total darkness.
I have to get out of here
on my own terms.
I don't wanna be pulled out
like the others.
Well, let's say we do
make it out of here, all right?
And we don't contract
the Saharan flu within hours.
We're still thousands
of miles apart
in a broken-down society.
Well, we need a meeting place.
We'd have to travel on foot.
Maybe we can find
working vehicles.
That's-- That's a huge maybe.
All right.
Four Corners Monument,
where Arizona, Colorado,
Utah and New Mexico meet.
No, that's too remote.
That's not safe.
That's not safe at all.
- I'll come to you.
- To Phoenix?
That's a whole state away.
I know, but I--
I'll make it work.
Is there a--
A government building,
something
that's centrally located?
- Yeah, City Hall.
- That's where we'll meet.
- Are you sure?
- Of course.
What about me?
You-- You can come, too.
I'm 3,000 miles away.
Never mind.
Just excess baggage.
I'll figure out
my own situation.
I'm sorry, Boston.
- Just one last thing, though.
- Sure.
We have to vote.
Seriously? You're still holding
on to that?
It's what we do.
It's what we did.
There's only three of us.
Pretty sure you know
how the vote turns out.
Please.
Just one last time.
Okay.
All those in favor of an escape.
Well, that's it, then.
Did you find the wires?
Yeah.
Let's do this.
Well, it did something.
I'm gonna try the door.
I'm going up.
No, Phoenix, wait!
I'll find you...
no matter what.
I love you, Phoenix.
I love you, too.
You're here.
Is this real?
I'm...
Oh, this is real.
This feels like a dream.
If this was a dream,
I wouldn't be here.
Yeah.
Hi.
You're taller than I expected.
How did we wind up next
to each other?
I don't know.
I don't know either.
I don't remember
this place.
Fifty-seven.
I mean,
maybe they moved us.
No, we would have known that.
Maybe we were here all along.
The others have
to be here somewhere, right?
Yeah, I... I don't know.
There.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my...
Phoenix.
Phoenix, come here.
Look over there.
Get down.
What are we gonna do?
We gotta find a way to get out
of here.
- No, I want answers.
- No, Phoenix,
we need to find a way out.
Someone knows what's going on.
Look, I will distract them.
Wait. What? Why?
Because they are blocking
the only exit.
Hey!
Go.
Wait, wait, wait.
Okay.
Phoenix, we shouldn't be here.
We need to go.
Not until I know
what this place is.
Look.
There.
Phoenix,
you sure about this?
Phoenix.
Phoenix, we need to go. Come on.
Let's go.
- Kimberly.
- Nadine?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, hey.
- Sit down, Dean.
What are you doing?
Put that down.
Put that down. Calm down.
Calm down, okay?
- Don't point that at him.
- Kimberly, get out of the way.
What are you doing?
This is crazy.
He is extremely dangerous.
He's not dangerous.
I know him. It's okay.
You don't know him at all.
- Okay.
- Okay, sit down.
All right.
Okay.
I just want to know
what's going on.
This is an experiment.
Kimberly,
you're still in prison.
You really expect
us to believe this bullshit?
- The epidemic was a lie.
- No.
No, it wasn't a lie.
It was a story.
I was...
I was trying to create
a better life.
And it worked.
It really worked.
What are you talking about?
I saw the news coverage.
- Yeah.
- We created that content
to make it more believable.
- "Content." Jesus.
- I don't understand.
How did you get me
from prison...
to my bunker?
Oh, we slipped sedatives
into your food,
flew you from Arizona,
and installed you here
the next day.
Where are we?
California.
You're fucking lying, bitch.
Why have you been forcing people
out of their bunkers?
They're shutting down Domain.
- Why?
- Because you banned Orlando.
- Who even knows about that?
- Everyone!
Someone leaked the video.
It blew up
on the Internet.
It was national news for weeks.
The media called you
"The Penthouse Prisoners."
They couldn't believe
how much freedom you had
in the prison environment.
It was ridiculous.
We were always in control.
That's not all.
The public hated
that you didn't know
you were in prison.
They thought the bunkers
were too nice.
They thought you were
getting off too lightly.
Never underestimate
humanity's capacity
to be punitive.
So they're just
shutting it down?
Yeah.
The public spoke.
The government
was only too happy to comply,
so they're pulling everyone out,
making some changes
in the bunkers and...
putting you back in
until they can find a space
- for you in the prison system.
- Oh, you fucking lying cunt.
- What is wrong with you?
- You're an escaped convict.
I have every legal right
to shoot you.
- Well, then do it.
- Denver, stop.
No. Shut up, Phoenix.
She's full of shit
and I'm calling her on it.
Why don't you tell her
why you're here?
Why are you here?
Denver.
- You don't wanna know.
- It's okay. You can tell me.
Trust me.
You're my one mistake.
Why me?
Why any of us?
Oh, you were one
of a thousand prisoners
that I specially selected
for the program.
Your psych evaluations indicated
that you would be very unlikely
to reveal your histories,
and you'd be the most likely
to believe the flu scenario.
I reasoned
that if we could control
your physical contact,
that you would put your past
behind you
and create new identities.
And you did.
Well, we were all lying
to each other.
Honey, everybody lies.
What did they do?
- Are you sure you wanna know?
- Yes.
They're my friends.
Well, Raymond Voss
was a career criminal.
He was in and out
of prison his whole life.
I think you know the rest
of his resume.
Hector Gonzales was in a gang.
He was directly responsible
for at least 20 murders.
Olivia Michaels was suffering
from postpartum depression
and she drowned
her three little girls,
right before she attempted
to commit suicide with pills.
Cedric Jackson was a prostitute
and a drug addict.
He murdered innumerable men
who paid to have sex with him,
stealing their cash,
their jewelry.
Barry O'Malley robbed a bank
with his two brothers.
Afterwards, they were trying
to divide the heist
and he murdered them both,
execution style.
And Denver?
Please tell me.
Dean Atkins stalked
and murdered 11 women
that he met
on various dating websites.
You know, I've heard
about people like you, Nadine.
Sure you're not a fan?
Seem to know a lot about us.
This program is my life,
my baby.
I watched all
of you every day for six years.
I know everything
about all of you.
I gave you a purpose,
a reason to live.
I gave you hope,
an opportunity to--
To put your past behind you
and to create something new,
a way to live your lives
in a humane atmosphere
instead of some prison
where the inmates are raped
and murdered.
This is worse.
It's only worse
because you found out.
You were never supposed
to find out.
- Ignorance is bliss, huh?
- Something like that.
- Nadine!
- In here.
Hands up.
For what it's worth, I'm sorry.
- Get up.
- Get off--
Wait. Wait--
No.
I'm here for you, Phoenix.
Hi.
You know, you've been out
for hours.
Okay, I get it.
The silent treatment, huh?
You know, Phoenix,
I'm still the same guy.
I actually believed you.
Believe what?
That you loved me.
Oh, I love you, Phoenix.
I love you in my way.
Did you love the women
you killed?
Yeah, for a while, sure.
Then why'd you kill them?
I can't explain that to you
in a way that you would find
accessible.
You knew that we were still
in prison.
Well,
I suspected it once you told me
about your mommy.
Of course,
I knew my own history...
...then Orlando.
I mean, three convicted felons
in one place, that's...
a little bit too much
of a coincidence.
So,
why didn't you say something?
It was fun.
It was fascinating
watching it all play out.
You're a sociopath.
Yeah, that's what they say.
And I was just another victim?
No. You were special.
Because you were the one
I could never have
the way I truly wanted.
On your feet. Let's move.
Well, well, well. Looky here.
We got the merry band
of frigging hypocrites. Hah!
Is that you, Atlanta?
Now, what'd you do,
Atlanta, huh?
You must have done
something pretty bad
to be put in here, right?
Hey, I wonder if it had anything
to do with those little angels.
I guess I'll be seeing y'all
in hell. Woo!
Come on.
No one else gets off
that easy.
Turn around.
Get in your cell.
Hey, Phoenix.
Don't worry.
I'll be right next door.
O Lord,
make me brave...
brave enough to face the dark...
the dark that works
to pull me in.
As the storm rages through...
let me rise above the gale
with bright eyes...
confident Thy way is wise.
Lord, make me brave...
brave enough to face the murk
of life.
Help me with my human plight.
Help me to retain my sight...
to know that from the dark
comes light.
To know that from the dark...
♪ You know who I am ♪
♪ He said ♪
♪ The speaker was an angel ♪
♪ He coughed
And shook his crumpled wings ♪
♪ Closed his eyes ♪
♪ And moved his lips ♪
♪ It's time we should be going ♪
♪ Waiting so long ♪
♪ I've been waiting so long ♪
♪ I've been waiting so
Waiting so ♪
♪ Waiting so ♪
♪ Look back in anger ♪
♪ Driven by the night ♪
♪ 'Til you come ♪
♪ Waiting so long ♪
♪ I've been waiting so long ♪
♪ I've been waiting so
Waiting so ♪
♪ Waiting so ♪
♪ Look back in anger ♪
♪ See it in my eyes ♪
♪ 'Til you come ♪
♪ No one seemed to hear him ♪
♪ So he leafed
Through a magazine ♪
♪ And yawning
Rubbed the sleep away ♪
♪ Very sane, he seemed to me ♪
♪ Waiting so long ♪
♪ I've been waiting so long ♪
♪ I've been waiting so
Waiting so ♪
♪ Waiting so ♪
♪ Look back in anger ♪
♪ Driven by the night ♪
♪ 'Til you come ♪
♪ Waiting so long ♪
♪ I've been waiting so long ♪
♪ I've been waiting so
Waiting so ♪
♪ Waiting so ♪
♪ Look back in anger ♪
♪ Feel it in my voice ♪
♪ Waiting so, waiting so ♪
♪ Waiting so ♪